When you're creating your layers for the vision, that happens a lot when you're doing pictures, and also when you're kind of building on a theme.
So, when we started with, "Money does grow on trees", it was important for me to really, visually express that and verbally express that.
So, that's why I got pictures of two trees.
Now, I didn't just pick one tree, because one isn't exactly what it says.
You want to be very specific in the layers of how you put your vision together.
And then I wanted to have lots of fun things growing on the trees, so I have $6,004,538.00 is one of the amounts of many growing on one of my trees.
Well, that makes me smile, I think that would make anyone smile.
And then, you know, adding "Go Green" and the little decorative hearts--things that are going to add to it so that you have some depth in what it is you're creating.
It's really, really important when you put these vision boards together that you go deeper into who you are as a person, that you really understand why is it that you want this.
And for me, if money is the root of generosity, my having more money gives me the ability to do more for more people.
So, even though this is incredibly materialistic, completely superficial, and totally "over-the-top", because it's just money and has nothing to do with anything but loving money, I can still take it in my vision board and bring it to a level where it really means something to me.
If I'm earning money and people are paying me to sing my music, I'm communicating something that really means something to me, that hopefully will benefit people in the world.
And if it's "just in time for spring", then I'm celebrating the world, I'm celebrating creation.
So, when you look at what you're putting into the board, make sure that you really have an understanding of while you're having fun with it, what it really means to you, because if you connect into it on an emotional level, then it's going to have more meaning for you.
And then, you're going to be able to have some really cool things show up in your life.